MUHAMMAD ALIF HIDAYATULLAH, WEB DEVELOPER

Pasuruan, Indonesia | +62 895-4061-69901 | malifh@proton.me | https://muhammadalifh.github.io/

SUMMARY

I am a Web Developer with 1 year of experience in developing information system websites using the Laravel framework and currently learning to use React. In addition, I have also completed several web projects with my team. I am currently focusing on web development and continue to learn new things to keep up with existing technology.

Surabaya, Indonesia

Jul 2019 - Aug 2023

Jakarta, Indonesia

Surabava

Malang

Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, PHP, SQL, Python

FrameWork: CodeIgniter, Laravel, React, Vue Miscellaneous Technologies: Git, Github

Interests: Watching, Gaming, Reading, Traveling, Football

EDUCATION

Surabaya State University, Bachelor of Applied Science

Major in Informatics Management

Cumulative GPA: 3.84/4.00

Relevant Coursework: Discrete Mathematics, Framework Programming

Orbit Future Academy, Independent Study Programs

Artificial Intelligence Mastery Program

Cumulative GPA: 4.00/4.00

Relevant Coursework: Data Science, Machine Learning, Reinforcement Learning

WORK EXPERIENCES

PT Andromedia Indonesia

Surabaya Feb 2022 – Jul 2022

Full-stack Developer - Internship

Perform tasks on the home page to make it responsive and flexible

Perform bug fixing on web pages that have been provided

PT Simetrie Digital Kreasi

Web Developer - Full Time Mar 2023 - Dec 2023

Develop responsive websites that suit the client's needs

Implement, manage and customize content using the WordPress CMS

Respond to requests for content changes or feature additions

PT Alfahuma Rekayasa Teknologi

PHP Programmer Junior - Full Time

Jan 2024 - Mar 2024

Building server-side software using the PHP back-end framework (Laravel)

Building client-side software using the Vue.js front-end framework

Implementing application integration via API

Programmer - Full Time

Surabaya PT Global Indo Inovatif Apr 2024 - Dec 2024

Developing an online shop in the company using the Framework (Laravel)

Integrate Frontend and Backend to connect via API

Developing an Online Store from the NVMEE.ID website platform

PROJECTS

MoKarva Mar 2021

MoKarya is an information system to monitor, accommodate, and show the results of the works that have been made by students

Jun 2021

Ringkas. Net is a Blog service provider website where users

can write and share inspiration with each other, and of course written in a concise manner

ManGo Jan 2021

ManGo is a website service for learning Japanese, there is also a feature of working on questions for users to make it easier to understand Japanese writing

This website created using Laravel

SIMPEL Apr 2022 SIMPEL is a web-based application that is intended to facilitate a price quote service with clients and to manage data from clients in a more structured manner Live Demo Bajak Laut dan Harta Karun yang hilang Jan 2022 Bajak Laut dan Harta Karun yang hilang is a 2D platformer game project Players are required to find keys in a level to unlock the hidden treasure This game project is done using Godot engine and uses the GDScript Play it here SIPELAKU (SISTEM PENGELOLAAN LABORATORIUM KULINER) Jul 2023 SIPELAKU is an information system used to facilitate the management of culinary laboratories in the D4 & S1 Tata Boga study programs at Surabaya State University Live Demo NVMEE Apr 2024 NVMEE is an online shop that sells goods especially for women such as hair straighteners, hair dryers, and several other make-up tools. Live Demo **ORGANIZATIONS** Member - Paskibra Elang Putih Jul 2016 – Jul 2019 Became the Chief Executive in the annual Won the Provincial Marching Skills competition Became a marching coach at the August 17th event Jun 2021 - Mar2022 Deputy Head of IT Division - Golek Mulya Aji 21 Became part of the IT division by creating and developing a blog-based website Provide information about the activities that have been carried out on the page website Member - FORMAPAS (Forum Mahasiswa Pasuruan) Oct 2021 -Aug 2022 Member of the Communication and Informatics division Be part of the Publication-Decoration-Documentation division of the webinar committee **CERTIFICATIONS AND ACHIEVEMENTS IT-Support Certification, Google** Sep 2022 The IT Support certification completes five courses developed by Google **Cloud Practitioner Essentials, Dicoding** Oct 2021 AWS Cloud certification held by dicoding about AWS Cloud with all types of service **Getting Started with Python, Dicoding** Oct 2020 Certificate of learning basic python programming with reference to current industry standards Coach CODE JAM, University State Of Surabaya Des 2020 Certificate given to the coach at the CODEJAM held by the Informatics Engineering Department Online Coding Bootcamp Backend SQL, Progate x Kominfo Oct 2021

Certificate of completion of online Bootcamp with SQL data programming language

Certificate of having completed the program and having fulfilled the requirement

Sep 2020

Program Vocational School Graduate Academy, Digitalent x Kominfo